dubaidutyfreetennischampionships.com 2019-07-08

# Privacy Policy - Dubai Duty Free Tennis Championships

**Dubai Duty Free Tennis Championships Website**

**General Privacy Information**

Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. Because we gather certain types of information about the users of dubaidutyfreetennischampionships.com and its associated digital products, such as the mobile website, email marketing and the like (collectively, the “Website”), we feel you should fully understand the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This Privacy Policy discloses and explains the privacy practices for this Website, what Personal Information and other information is collected from and about you, how the information is used, and with whom we may share such information. By visiting this Website, and/or using the services offered on or through this Website, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy as they may be amended from time to time. If you are located in the European Union (“EU”), you will be asked to provide clear and unequivocal affirmative consent to the collection, processing, and sharing of your “Personal Information” (defined below) via cookies and similar technologies. The services on this Website may change and expand, and this Privacy Policy may change accordingly, so check back occasionally.

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information that you may provide, or that we may obtain, other than through this Website, such as by phone, through postal mail and through other live and print media. Also, this Privacy Policy only addresses the activities from our own servers. Other websites (including but not limited to those websites that may be linked to this Website) may have their own privacy policies and practices, which we do not control.

The Website is owned and operated by Dubai Duty Free.

Notice to EU Individuals:  This Privacy Policy and its enumerated policies are intended to comply with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 (the “General Data Protection Regulation” or “GDPR”) and provide appropriate protection and care with respect to the treatment of your Personal Information in accordance with the GDPR.  We are the “controller” of Personal Information for the purposes of the GDPR.

**Privacy Policy Purpose**

To make your visits to this Website and use of the services available as purposeful as possible, you may be asked for personal information and certain information may be collected from your computer when you visit us. “Personal Information” includes, for example, your name, email address and IP address to name a few.

We are committed to protecting the information we collect so this Website’s users can feel confident about using this Website to explore the range of information, promotions, services and products we offer. This Website is hosted in a secure environment and the servers/systems are configured with industry-standard firewalls.

**Right to Opt In and Opt Out**

You may have the right to “opt in” and “opt out” of certain of our uses of your Personal Information. For example, at the time you are requested to provide Personal Information on this Website, you may have the opportunity to elect to, or not to, receive correspondence from us. You may opt out of any communication with us by clicking the general opt-out link in our communications or by sending an email as outlined in the “Contact Us” section below stating that you would like to be removed from a specific list, or all communications. However, please understand that you may still be contacted by us in connection with your client relationship or as follow up from an event or activity.

**The Following Information is Collected by Us**

  1. **User-Provided Information**

We collect Personal Information from and about users of this Website, for example, through such users’ activities, surveys, and completion of online forms on this Website. Such information is collected, for example, when users register or subscribe for accreditation, accounts or features on this Website, complete surveys, that we may make available on or through this Website, submit a comment or question to us using a “contact us” or similar feature on this Website, send us an email, or in any other way submit Personal Information to us via this Website.

**Website Use Information**

We may use “cookies” to keep, and sometimes track, information about you. Cookies are small data files that are sent to your browser or related software from a web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies include analytics that provide us data that allows us to better understand our users and improve the Website based on what we have learned from that data.

Cookies track where you travel on this Website and what you look at. A cookie may enable us to relate your use of this Website to other information about you, including your Personal Information. All of these purposes serve to improve and personalize your experience on this Website. Most web browsers can be set to inform you when a cookie has been sent to you and provide you with the opportunity to refuse that cookie. However, refusing a cookie may, in some cases, preclude you from using, or negatively impact the display or function of, this Website or certain areas or features of this Website.  For EU individuals, cookies also help inform us whether you require, or have already been served, an affirmative consent request in connection with the GDPR.

  3. **IP Address and Click-through Information**

Our servers collect data about your server’s Internet address automatically when you visit us. This information, known as an Internet Protocol Address, or IP Address, is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider whenever you are on the Internet. When you request pages from this Website, our servers may log your IP Address and sometimes your domain name. Our servers may also record the referring page that linked you to us; the pages you visit on this Website; the website you visit after this Website; the ads you see and/or click on; other information about the type of web browser, computer, platform, related software and settings you are using; any search terms you have entered on this Website or a referral site; and other web usage activity and data logged by our servers. We use this information for internal system administration, to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer this Website. Such information may also be used to gather broad demographic information, such as country of origin and Internet Service Provider. We may also link this information with your Personal Information. Any or all of these activities with regard to website usage information may be performed on our behalf by our service providers.

**How We Use Your Personal Information; Updating**

We will use your Personal Information, for example, to respond to your requests and to provide you with our product and service offerings. We may also use your Personal Information to maintain our internal record keeping. We may match information collected from you through different means or at different times, including both personal information and website usage information, and use such information along with information obtained from other sources, including third parties. In addition, we may send you notices (for example, in the form of emails, mailings, and the like, such as our e-newsletters), and otherwise correspond with you, about products, services, companies and events, sponsored by us and others, that we think might interest you. You may opt out of receiving such notices from us by following the instructions in the right to  **Opt In and Opt Out**  section above. We may analyze user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, this Website and emails, both on an individual basis and in the aggregate. In general, other than as set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share Personal Information with third parties.

**Service Providers**

We may use third-party partners to help operate this Website and deliver our products and services such as buying the tickets online and may share your information with our affiliates, service providers and other third parties that provide products or services for or through this Website or for our business (such as website or database hosting companies, address list hosting companies, email service providers, analytics companies, distribution companies, fulfillment companies, and other similar service providers that use such information on our behalf).

**Aggregate Statistics**

We may disclose aggregate statistics regarding user behavior as a measure of interest in, and use of, this Website and emails to third parties in the form of aggregate data, such as overall patterns or demographic reports that do not describe or identify any individual user.

**Legally Compelled Disclosures**

We may disclose user information to government authorities, and to other third parties when compelled to do so by government authorities, at our discretion, or otherwise as required or permitted by law, including but not limited to in response to court orders and subpoenas. We also may disclose user information when we have reason to believe that someone is causing injury to or interference with our rights or property, other users of this Website, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities.

**Security**

While we will endeavor to protect the security and integrity of sensitive Personal Information provided to this Website, due to the inherent nature of the Internet as an open global communications vehicle, we cannot guarantee that information, during transmission through the Internet or while stored on our system or otherwise in our care, will be absolutely safe from intrusion by others, such as hackers. If you contact us by email or a “contact us” or similar feature on this Website, you should be aware that your transmission might not be secure. A third party could view information you send by these methods in transit. Do not send sensitive information (such as payment card information, social security numbers, employer identification numbers, passwords, or pin numbers) to us via email or via a “contact us” or similar feature on this Website. We will have no liability for disclosure of your information due to errors or unauthorized acts of third parties during or after transmission. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your Personal Information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development. If a notification is appropriate, we would endeavor to do so as promptly as possible under the circumstances, and, to the extent we have your email address, we may notify you by email. You consent to our use of email as a means of such notification.

**Third-Party “Linked-To” Websites**

We have engaged to third -party vendors with non-disclosure agreement for our online ticket sales and accreditation portal. When you are on this Website you may have the opportunity to visit, or link to, other websites, or other electronic media not operated by us. These sites may collect personal information about you. We do not control sites that are operated by these entities and is not responsible for the information practices of the other websites. The privacy policies of any linked websites are the sole responsibility of the other websites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy, or any other of our policies or practices, at any time, and will notify users of this Website by posting such changed or updated Privacy Policy on this page. Any changes or updates will be effective immediately upon posting to this Website. Under certain circumstances, we may also elect to notify you of changes or updates to our Privacy Policy by additional means, such as posting a notice on the front page of this Website or sending you an email.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or comments regarding our privacy policies and practices, or to exercise any of your rights as described in this Privacy Policy or under data protection laws (including, without limitation, the GDPR), you may contact us at:

Dubai Duty Free

P.O. Box 831

Dubai, UAE

Email: [Marketing@ddf.ae](mailto:Marketing@ddf.ae)
